Guide to the Annie Stein Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Files
  - Textbooks, 1969-1974, (2 Folders) (Box 18, Folder 13 to 14)
  - Evaluations--Title I, 1968-1975, (2 Folders) (Box 18, Folder 15 to 16)
  - Baum Case Appeal, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - UFT Positions Before and After Strike, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Black Teachers and Staff, 1970-1977, (2 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 3 to 4)
  - Teachers--Composition and Placement, 1967-1971 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Tests and Testing, 1961-1973, (2 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 6 to 7)
  - Education Technology, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Citywide Council for Quality Education, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - SESPA, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Community District 23, 1970-1972 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Data for Reading Failure Lecture, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Course on Racism and Education, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - District One, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Reading Crisis, 1962-1972, (2 Folders) (Box 20, Folder 3 to 4)
  - Integration, 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Parents Workshop, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Commission on Integration--Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Decentralization Debate--Post-strike, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - More Effective Schools, 1964-1969 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Andrew Jackson High School, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Reports and Newsletters, 1963-1978 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Intermediate School 201, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Brownsville School Data, 1965-1969 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Commissioner’s Orders, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Galamison Appeal Documents, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Brownsville Education Park Suit, 1966-1968 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Utilization Reports, 1963-1969, (2 Folders) (Box 22, Folder 3 to 4)
  - Utilization Reports, 1969-1973 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Fact Books and Reports, 1968-1975, (3 Folders) (Box 23, Folder 2 to 4)
  - Fact Books and Reports, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Business and Administrative Curriculum, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Hobson Case, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Harlem Parents Suit, 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Reverse Discrimination, 1974-1977 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - School Board Elections, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - School Construction Scandals, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Education Parks, 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Integration Construction Budget, 1963-1965 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Allen Plan, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Official Documents--Open Enrollment, 1957-1962 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Official Statements, 1962-1963 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Community Control--Bills and Formal Actions, 1965-1971 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - School Year, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Parents’ Rights, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Students’ Rights, 1969, (2 Folders) (Box 25, Folder 8 to 9)
  - Students’ Rights, 1969-1973 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Public School Ethnic Composition--Tabular Data, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Legal Action, 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Puerto Rican Data, 1963-1971, (3 Folders) (Box 26, Folder 4 to 6)
  - Ritalin, 1971-1974 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Fleischman, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Reports, 1958-1974 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Reports, 1962-1973, (2 Folders) (Box 27, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Legal Action, 1960-1983, (3 Folders) (Box 27, Folder 3 to 5)
  - Capitalism and Crisis, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Learn English Campaign, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Staff Survey, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Reports, 1962-1972 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Legal Action, 1969-1976 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Baum, Jeanne Case, 1973-1978
    - Baum, Jean Video, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Baum Trial Testimony, 1975, (3 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 1 to 3)
    - Legal Documents, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Legal Documents, 1975-1978, (3 Folders) (Box 30, Folder 1 to 3)
  - Achievement--Reading, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - East New York Educational Complex--Master Plan, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Staff Data--Department of Health Education and Welfare, 1971-1979
    - H.E.W.--NY Schools, 1977-1979 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Reports, 1971-1979, (3 Folders) (Box 31, Folder 3 to 5)
  - Stein, Annie--Personal
    - Resume, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Car Accident, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Career Ed, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 8)